Guide to the M. Moran Weston Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: St. Philip's Church
  - Business correspondence, January - February 1962 (Box 22, Folder 151)
  - Business correspondence, March - April 1962 (Box 22, Folder 152)
  - Business correspondence, May - June 1962 (Box 22, Folder 153)
  - Business correspondence, July - August 1962 (Box 22, Folder 154)
  - Business correspondence, September - October 1962 (Box 22, Folder 155)
  - Business correspondence, November - December 1962 (Box 22, Folder 156)
  - Business correspondence, January - June 1963 (Box 23, Folder 157)
  - Business correspondence, July - December 1963 (Box 23, Folder 158)
  - Business correspondence, January - December 1964 (Box 23, Folder 159)
  - Business correspondence, January - December 1965 (Box 23, Folder 160)
  - Business correspondence, January - December 1966 (Box 23, Folder 161)
  - Business correspondence, January - August 1967 (Box 23, Folder 162)
  - Business correspondence, September - December 1967 (Box 23, Folder 163)
  - Business correspondence, January - August 1968 (Box 24, Folder 164)
  - Business correspondence, September 1968 (Box 24, Folder 165)
  - Business correspondence, October - December 1968 (Box 24, Folder 166)
  - Business correspondence, January 1969 (Box 24, Folder 167)
  - Business correspondence, February and March 1969 (Box 24, Folder 168)
  - Business correspondence, April - August 1969 (Box 24, Folder 169)
  - Business correspondence relating to the State Office Building, Summer and Fall 1969 (Box 25, Folder 170)
  - Business correspondence, September - December 1969 (Box 25, Folder 171)
  - Business correspondence, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 172)
  - Business correspondence, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 173)
  - Business correspondence, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 174)
  - Business correspondence, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 175)
  - Business correspondence, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 176)
  - Business correspondence, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 177)
  - Business correspondence, January - June 1976 (Box 26, Folder 178)
  - Business correspondence, July - October 1976 (Box 26, Folder 179)
  - Business correspondence, November and December 1976 (Box 26, Folder 180)
  - Business correspondence, [n.d.] and 1977 (Box 27, Folder 181)
  - Business correspondence, January 1977 (Box 27, Folder 182)
  - Business correspondence, February and March 1977 (Box 27, Folder 183)
  - Business correspondence, April and May 1977 (Box 27, Folder 184)
  - Business correspondence, June - August 1977 (Box 27, Folder 185)
  - Business correspondence, September 1977 (Box 28, Folder 186)
  - Business correspondence, October 1977 (Box 28, Folder 187)
  - Business correspondence, November 1977 (Box 28, Folder 188)
  - Business correspondence relating to Percy Sutton's campaign for Mayor, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 189)
  - Business correspondence, December 1977 (Box 28, Folder 190)
  - Business correspondence, [n.d.] and 1978 (Box 29, Folder 191)
  - Business correspondence, January 1978 (Box 29, Folder 192)
  - Business correspondence, February and March 1978 (Box 29, Folder 193)
  - Business correspondence, April and June 1978 (Box 29, Folder 194)
  - Business correspondence, July and August 1978 (Box 29, Folder 195)
  - Business correspondence, September 1978 (Box 30, Folder 196)
  - Business correspondence, October 1978 (Box 30, Folder 197)
  - Business correspondence, November 1978 (Box 30, Folder 198)
  - Business correspondence, 1-15 December 1978 (Box 30, Folder 199)
  - Business correspondence, 16-31 December 1978 (Box 30, Folder 200)
  - Business correspondence, [n.d.] and 1979 (Box 31, Folder 201)
  - Business correspondence, January 1979 (Box 31, Folder 202)
  - Business correspondence, February 1979 (Box 31, Folder 203)
  - Business correspondence, March 1979 (Box 31, Folder 204)
  - Business correspondence, April and May 1979 (Box 31, Folder 205)
  - United Nations. Special Commission Against Apartheid Correspondence, notes & reports, etc. 22-25 May 1979, (2 folders) (Box 32, Folder 206 & 207)
  - Business correspondence, June 1979 (Box 32, Folder 208)
  - Business correspondence, July 1979 (Box 32, Folder 209)
  - Business correspondence, August 1979 (Box 32, Folder 210)
  - Business correspondence, September 1979 (Box 33, Folder 211)
  - Business correspondence, October 1979 (Box 33, Folder 212)
  - Business correspondence, November-December 1979 (Box 33, Folder 213)
  - Business correspondence Newsletter of the Investor Responsiblity Research Center, June 1979 - March 1982 (Box 33, Folder 214)
  - Business correspondence, Undated 1980 (Box 34, Folder 215)
  - Business correspondence, January - March 1980 (Box 34, Folder 216)
  - Business correspondence, April - June 1980 (Box 34, Folder 217)
  - Business correspondence, July - September 1980 (Box 34, Folder 218)
  - Business correspondence, October 1980 (Box 34, Folder 219)
  - Business correspondence, November 1980 (Box 35, Folder 220)
  - Business correspondence, November 1980 (Box 35, Folder 221)
  - Business correspondence, December 1980 (Box 35, Folder 222)
  - Business correspondence, Undated 1981 (Box 35, Folder 223)
  - Business correspondence, January - April 1981 (Box 35, Folder 224)
  - Business correspondence, May - June 1981 (Box 36, Folder 225)
  - Business correspondence Re: International Sanctions Against South Africa, 20 - 27 May 1981 (Box 36, Folder 226)
  - Business correspondence Re: International Sanctions Against South Africa, 20 - 27 May 1981 (Box 36, Folder 227)
  - Business correspondence, July - October 1981 (Box 36, Folder 228)
  - Business correspondence, November 1981 (Box 37, Folder 229)
  - Business correspondence, December 1981 (Box 37, Folder 230)
  - Business correspondence, Undated 1982 (Box 37, Folder 231)
  - Business correspondence, January 1-15, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 232)
  - Business correspondence, January 16-31, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 233)
  - Business correspondence, February 1982 (Box 37, Folder 234)
  - Business correspondence, March - April 1982 (Box 38, Folder 235)
  - Business correspondence, May - August 1982 (Box 38, Folder 236)
  - Business correspondence, September - Decmber 1982 (Box 38, Folder 237)
  - Business correspondence, 1983 - 1988 (Box 38, Folder 238)
  - Business correspondence Business and Professional Women'n Club, 1960 - 1963 (Box 38, Folder 239)
  - Business correspondence Rev. Allen Hinman, 1976 - 1978 (Box 38, Folder 240)
  - Business correspondence Ms. Nanette Taylor, 1977 - 1978 (Box 38, Folder 241)
  - Business correspondence Rev. Allen Hinman, 1979 - 1981 (Box 38, Folder 242)
  - Press releases, undated drafts and releases, 1950-1959 (Box 39, Folder 243)
  - Press releases, 1960-1969 (Box 39, Folder 244)
  - Press releases, 1970-1980 (Box 39, Folder 245)
  - Church Newsletters, 1950-1969 (Box 39, Folder 246)
  - Church Newsletters, 1974-1985 (Box 39, Folder 247)
  - Annual Fellowship Day and Annual Fellowship Dinners and Luncheons, 1932 and 1960-1969 (Box 40, Folder 248)
  - Annual Fellowship Luncheons, 1970-1974 (Box 40, Folder 249)
  - Annual Fellowship Luncheon, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 250)
  - Annual Fellowship Luncheon, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 251)
  - Annual Fellowship Luncheon, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 252)
  - Annual Fellowship Luncheons, 1978 and 1979 (Box 41, Folder 253)
  - Annual Fellowship Luncheons, 1980 and 1981 (Box 41, Folder 254)
  - Annual Fellowship Luncheons, 1982 and 1983 (Box 41, Folder 255)
  - Luncheon programs from other churches, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 256)
  - Procedures for special religious services miscellaneous. (Box 42, Folder 257)
  - Procedures for special religious services Eucharist. (Box 42, Folder 258)
  - Procedures for special religious services Confirmation. (Box 42, Folder 259)
  - Procedures for special religious services Marriage. (Box 42, Folder 260)
  - Procedures for special religious services Funeral. (Box 42, Folder 261)
  - Procedures for special religious services - Memorial. (Box 42, Folder 262)
  - Procedures for special religious services - Corporate Communion for College Students. (Box 42, Folder 263)
  - Procedures for special religious services - Institution of Priests. (Box 42, Folder 264)
  - Installation of Warden and Vestry. (Box 42, Folder 265)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Epiphany. (Box 42, Folder 266)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Candlemas. (Box 42, Folder 267)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Lent. (Box 42, Folder 268)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Palm Sunday. (Box 42, Folder 269)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Easter. (Box 42, Folder 270)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Whitsunday (Pentecost). (Box 42, Folder 271)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Catronal Festival. (Box 42, Folder 272)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Homecoming Sunday. (Box 42, Folder 273)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Thanksgiving. (Box 42, Folder 274)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Annual Candlelight Service. (Box 42, Folder 275)
  - Procedures for Special Religious Services - Christmas. (Box 42, Folder 276)
  - Schedules for Officiating at Services. (Box 42, Folder 277)
  - Schedules for Acolytes. (Box 42, Folder 278)
  - Attendance Reords at Services. (Box 42, Folder 278A)
  - Services by Visiting Ministers. (Box 42, Folder 279)
  - Music for Church Services. (Box 42, Folder 280)
  - Concerts, 1956 - 1974 (Box 42, Folder 281)
  - Concerts, 1975 - (Box 42, Folder 282)
  - Pastoral Concerns, 1953 - 1960 (Box 43, Folder 283)
  - Pastoral Concerns, 1961 - 1969 (Box 43, Folder 284)
  - Pastoral Concerns, 1970 - 1976 (Box 43, Folder 285)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Church Guestbook, 1970 - 1975 (Box 43, Folder 286)
  - Pastoral Concerns, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 287)
  - Pastoral Concerns, 1980 - 1982 (Box 44, Folder 289)
  - Pastoral Concerns, 1983 - 1990 (Box 44, Folder 290)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, 1960, A - H (Box 44, Folder 291)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, 1960, I - Z (Box 44, Folder 292)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, 1961, S - Z (Box 44, Folder 293)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, 1961, A - R (Box 44, Folder 294)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, 1962, T - Z (Box 45, Folder 295)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, Early 1960s (Box 45, Folder 296)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, Early 1960s (Box 45, Folder 297)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, Early 1960s (Box 45, Folder 298)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, Early 1960s (Box 46, Folder 300)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 301)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, [v.d.] (Box 46, Folder 302)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, [v.d.] (Box 46, Folder 303)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Correspondence, [v.d.] (Box 46, Folder 304)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Condolence Letters, 1973 - 1975 (Box 47, Folder 306)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Parishoners' Thank-You Notes, Late 1970s (Box 47, Folder 307)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Letters of Transfer Into Saint Philips, 1957 - 1961 (Box 47, Folder 308)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Letters of Transfer Into Saint Philips Pending, 1959 - 1961 (Box 47, Folder 309)
  - Pastoral Concerns - Letters of Transfer Out of Saint Philips, 1957 - 1961 (Box 47, Folder 310)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1949 - 1956 (Box 48, Folder 311)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1957 - 1958 (Box 48, Folder 312)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1959 - 1960 (Box 48, Folder 313)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 314)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 315)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1963 - 1964 (Box 49, Folder 316)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1964- 1966 (Box 49, Folder 317)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1967 - 1968 (Box 49, Folder 318)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 319)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 320)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 321)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 322)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 323)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 324)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 325)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 326)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 327)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 328)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 329)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 330)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 331)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 332)
  - Church Bulletins and Announcements, 1985 - 1988 (Box 52, Folder 333)
  - MAS Breakfast Group, 1980 - 1981 (Box 53, Folder 334)
  - Breakfast Group, 1977 - 1989 (Box 53, Folder 335)
  - Breakfast Group, 1990 - 1992 (Box 53, Folder 336)
  - Breakfast Group, 1993 - 1995 (Box 53, Folder 337)
  - Materials from Other Churches, 1932 - 1984 (Box 53, Folder 338)
  - Shelton Hale Bishop Personal Papers and Correspondence (Box 169)
  - Saint Philip's Church Marraiges - Confidential (Box 172, Folder 948)
  - Private Letters from Parishioners (Box 172, Folder 949)
  - Confidential Papers re: Reginald Davis (Box 172, Folder 950)
  - Confidential - Parish Business & Letters from Parishioners (Box 172, Folder 951)
  - Letters from Parishioners, 1950-1973 (Box 172, Folder 952)
  - Saint Philip's Church Leaflets, 1982 - 1984 (Box 173, Folder 954)
  - State of New York Correspondence Papers etc. (Box 173, Folder 955)
  - Saint Philip's Church Miscellaneous Papers (Box 173, Folder 960)
  - Various Church Papers (Box 173, Folder 961)
  - Saint Philip's Church Miscellaneous Papers (Box 174, Folder 963)
  - Saint Philip's Church Breakfast Group Papers (Box 174, Folder 965)
  - Saint Philip's Church Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 174, Folder 966)
  - Saint Philip's Church Badges for Various Church Organizations (Box 174, Folder 969)
  - Cuttington College and Divinity School Correspondence, Monrovia, Liberia, (Book) (Box 174, Folder 971)
- Series VI: Community Service Council of Greater Harlem
  - Blank Forms. (Box 54, Folder 339)
  - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1961 -1962, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 340)
  - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 341)
  - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 342)
  - Board of Directors - Minutes and Correspondence, 1973 - 1978 (Box 54, Folder 343)
  - Financial Statements, 1960 - 1969 (Box 54, Folder 344)
  - Financial Statements, 1971 - 1979 (Box 54, Folder 345)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1977 - 1981 (Box 55, Folder 346)
  - Business Correspondence - Assurance Dinner, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 347)
  - Business Correspondence, 1957 - 1961 (Box 55, Folder 348)
  - Business Correspondence, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 349)
  - Business Correspondence, 1968 - 1969 (Box 55, Folder 350)
  - Business Correspondence, 1970 - 1972 (Box 55, Folder 351)
  - Business Correspondence, 1973 - 1974 (Box 56, Folder 352)
  - Business Correspondence, 1975 - 1976 (Box 56, Folder 353)
  - Business Correspondence, January - June 1977 (Box 56, Folder 354)
  - Business Correspondence, July - December 1977 (Box 56, Folder 355)
  - Business Correspondence, January - June 1978 (Box 57, Folder 356)
  - Business Correspondence, July - October 1978 (Box 57, Folder 357)
  - Business Correspondence, November - December 1978 (Box 57, Folder 358)
  - Business Correspondence, January - March 1979 (Box 57, Folder 359)
  - Business Correspondence, April - July 1979 (Box 57, Folder 360)
  - Business Correspondence, September - December 1979 (Box 57, Folder 361)
  - Business Correspondence, January - June 1980 (Box 58, Folder 362)
  - Business Correspondence, August - December 1980 (Box 58, Folder 363)
  - Business Correspondence, January - September 1981 (Box 58, Folder 364)
  - Business Correspondence, October - December 1981 (Box 58, Folder 365)
  - Business Correspondence, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 366)
  - Business Correspondence, 1983 - 1985 (Box 59, Folder 367)
  - Business Correspondence, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 368)
  - Business Correspondence, 1986 - 1989 (Box 59, Folder 369)
  - Materials Related to Harlem Youth Opportunities Unlimited Inc. (HARYOU), 1964 - 1966 (Box 59, Folder 370)
  - Fund-Raising Materials, Mid to Late 1960s. (Box 60, Folder 371)
  - Fund-Raising Proposals From Other Organizations. (Box 60, Folder 372)
  - St. Philip's Community Center Blank Stationery and Forms. (Box 60, Folder 373)
  - St. Philip's Community Center Business Correspondence, 1954 - 1961 (Box 60, Folder 374)
  - St. Philip's Community Center Business Correspondence, 1962 - 1969 (Box 60, Folder 375)
  - St. Philip's Community Center Business Correspondence, 1970 - 1974 (Box 60, Folder 376)
  - St. Philip's Community Center Business Correspondence, 1975-1985 (Box 61, Folder 377)
  - St. Philip's Community Center Correspondence with vendors A-N (Box 61, Folder 378)
  - St. Philip's Community Center Correspondence with vendors O-Z (Box 61, Folder 379)
  - St. Philip's Community Center Construction of new building, 1964-1968 (Box 61, Folder 380)
  - St. Philip's Other H.A.L.F. Business correspondence, 1976 and 1977 (Box 62, Folder 381a)
  - St. Philip's Other H.A.L.F. Business correspondence, January - June 1978 (Box 62, Folder 382)
  - St. Philip's Other H.A.L.F. Business correspondence, July - December 1978 (Box 62, Folder 383)
  - St. Philip's Other H.A.L.F. Business correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 62, Folder 384)
  - St. Philip's In-School Out-Of-School programs, 1979-1981 (Box 62, Folder 385)
  - St. Philip's Summer Youth programs, 1979-1981 (Box 62, Folder 386)
  - Upper Manhattan Day Care and Child Developement Center Stationary (blank) (Box 63, Folder 387)
  - Upper Manhattan Day Care and Child Developement Center Financial statements, 1974 and 1975 (Box 63, Folder 388)
  - Upper Manhattan Day Care and Child Developement Center. Board of Directors Minutes and communications, 1973 and 1974 (Box 63, Folder 389)
  - Upper Manhattan Day Care and Child Developement Center. Business correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 63, Folder 390)
  - Upper Manhattan Day Care and Child Developement Center. Business correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 63, Folder 391)
  - Upper Manhattan Day Care and Child Developement Center. Business correspondence, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 392)
  - Upper Manhattan Day Care and Child Developement Center. Business correspondence, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 393)
  - Upper Manhattan Day Care and Child Developement Center. Business correspondence, 1979 and 1980 (Box 63, Folder 394)
  - Upper Manhattan Day Care and Child Developement Center. Business correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 63, Folder 395)
- Series VII: Housing
  - Correspondence related to general housing issues, 1933-1979 (Box 64, Folder 396)
  - Correspondence related to general housing issues, 1981-1985 (Box 64, Folder 397)
  - Correspondence related to general housing issues, 1986-1988 (Box 64, Folder 398)
  - Correspondence related to general housing issues, 1987-1996 (Box 64, Folder 399)
  - Correspondence related to unspecified buildings, [v.d.] (Box 64, Folder 400)
  - 135th Street Apartments, 1953-1969 (Box 65, Folder 401)
  - 135th Street Apartments, 1971-1975 (Box 65, Folder 402)
  - 135th Street Apartments, 1976-1978 (Box 65, Folder 403)
  - 135th Street Apartments, August-December 1979 (Box 65, Folder 404)
  - 135th Street Apartments, January-July 1979 (Box 65, Folder 405)
  - 135th Street Apartments, 1980-1991 (Box 65, Folder 406)
  - St. Philip's Housing Board Meetings, 1978 and 1979 (Box 66, Folder 407)
  - St. Philip's On The Park. Board of Directors Meeting, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 408)
  - St. Philip's On The Park. Financial statements, 1977-1994 (Box 66, Folder 409)
  - St. Philip's On The Park. Developement and construction, 1968-1977 (Box 66, Folder 410)
  - St. Philip's On The Park. Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 1990-1994 (Box 67, Folder 414)
  - St. Philip's On The Park II. Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 1980 (Box 67, Folder 415)
  - St. Philip's Senior House. Board of Directors Munutes, 1978-1986 (Box 67, Folder 416)
  - St. Philip's Senior House Financial statements, 1978-1990 (Box 67, Folder 417)
  - St. Philip's Senior House Correspondence, memos., etc., [n.d.] and 1969-1979, (2 folders) (Box 67, Folder 418 & 419)
  - St. Philip's Senior House General correspondence, 1980-1989, (5 folders) (Box 68, Folder 420 - 424)
  - St. Philip's Senior House General correspondence, 1990 - 1994, (4 folders) (Box 69, Folder 425 - 428)
  - Greater Harlem Nursing Home. Board of Directors Minutes, 1986 and 1987 (Box 70, Folder 429)
  - Greater Harlem Nursing Home Correspondence and documents, 1970-1973 (Box 70, Folder 430)
  - Demov, Morris, Levin & Shein Report of Closing. Greater Harlem Nursing Home Company Inc., 1973, (1 volume) (Box 70)
    [Project No. SNY - 96]
  - Greater Harlem Nursing Home Correspondence and documents, 1974-1983, (3 folders) (Box 70, Folder 431-433)
  - Greater Harlem Nursing Home Correspondence and documents, 1984-1991, (5 folders) (Box 71, Folder 434-438)
  - Bishop House Correspondence and documents, 1980-1985, (6 folders) (Box 72, Folder 439-444)
  - Bishop House Correspondence and documents, 1986-1988, (4 folders) (Box 73, Folder 444-447)
  - St. Philip's Senior House Report and correspondence (Box 74, Folder 448)
  - Hirschen & Singer Bishop House. St. Philip's/Harlem Hospital. Final Endorsement, 3 February 1989, (1 volume) (Box 74, Folder 449)
  - Bishop House Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 1989-1993, (4 folders) (Box 74, Folder 450-453)
  - Weston Terrace Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 1981-1986, (5 folders) (Box 75, Folder 455-459)
    [a.k.a. St. Philips on Convent Avenue; Logan Gardens; Logan Hospital]
  - Weston Terrace Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 1988 and 1989, (3 folders) (Box 76, Folder 460-462)
  - Weston Terrace Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 1989-1993, (7 folders) (Box 77, Folder 463-469)
  - Weston House Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 203 West 13th Street, 1987-1993, (4 folders) (Box 78, Folder 470-473)
  - Weston House. Transitional Living Center Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 2262 Adam Clayton Powell, Jr. Blvd., 1990-1993, (4 folders) (Box 79, Folder 474-477)
  - Weston House. Transitional Living Center Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 2262 Adam Clayton Powell, Jr. Blvd., 1985-1990, (5 folders) (Box 80, Folder 478-482)
  - Urban Gardens Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 1987-1991, (3 folders) (Box 81, Folder 483-485)
  - Psychosocial Club Reports, correspondence, memos., etc., 1991 (Box 81, Folder 486)
  - Weston United Community Renewal, Inc. Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 1988-1990, (3 folder) (Box 82, Folder 487-489)
  - Weston United Community Renewal, Inc. Reports, correspondence, memos., etc. 1991-1993, (5 folders) (Box 83, Folder 490-494)
  - Weston United Community Renewal, Inc. Budgetary and Salary Information (Box 171, Folder 944)
  - Christian Social Relations Correspondence, Papers etc. (Box 173, Folder 957)
  - Dr. M. Moran Weston Papers on Housing & Urban Development (Box 173, Folder 959)
  - Westin United Community Renewal Inc. Correspondence, reports, papers, etc. 1994 - 1996 (Box 84, Folder 495-499)
  - Towers on the Park Correspondence, memos., documents, etc. 1983-1986, (6 folders) (Box 85, Folder 500-505)
  - Towers on the Park Correspondence, memos., documents, etc. 1987-1989, (4 folders) (Box 86, Folder 506-509)